nileguide.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy

At Nileguide.com ("Company"), we know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By accessing the Company website and using the services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**   
This Privacy Policy covers Company´s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Company gathers when you are on the Nileguide.com website and when you use the services, including registration based features. The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, street address, email address, birth year, gender, city, state, zip code, country, and travel destinations. 

Also, this Policy covers the Company´s treatment of any Personal Information that the Company´s business partners share with the Company. This Policy does not apply to the practices of third party service providers with which Company may partner but does not own or control, or to individuals that Company does not employ or manage. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Company Collect?**   
Our primary goal in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We may collect the following types of information from our customers: 

**Information You Provide to Us:**   
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain features and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new services. 

Registration: In order for you to use our registration-based services, you must complete a registration form. We require your contact information (such as screen name and email address). We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized service. 

**Automatic Information:**   
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via our website. The Company automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs including your IP address, cookie information, the page you requested, and your communications and interactions with other site registrants. The Company uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the service. 

The Company´s service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and use of the service components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the service, so we can make the service appealing to as many customers as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our service. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their areas and our service, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal experience. 

We also collect and use information for internal purposes. For example, if you are a registered user of the Company´s registration based services, we may keep records in your account history of your use of the registration based features, and any reported violation of our Terms of Service that you or someone on your account may have committed. 

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit web sites anonymously. While Company will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

**E-mail Communications:**   
We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from the Company if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with news or promotions. If you are a registered user of the Company´s registration-based services and do not want to receive e-mail from us, please do not opt in to receive these emails. However, if you do opt-in, you may later unsubscribe by following the Company´s procedures listed at the bottom of such email. 

**Information From Other Sources:**   
For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

**What about Cookies?**   
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer´s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Company cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your account name or email address is. 

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Company´s most attractive features. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Will Company Share Any of the Information it Receives?**   
We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only with the entities that are controlled by or control the Company and as described below. 

**Affiliated Business We Do Not Control:**   
We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses operate within the Company´s service or sell items or services to you within the Company´s service. In other situations, the Company provides services, or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business only when necessary. 

**Agents:**   
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples may include, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. 

**Promotional Offers:**   
We may send offers to certain customers on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you are a registered user of the Company´s subscription based services and do not wish to receive these offers, please do not opt in to receive these emails. However, if you do opt-in, you may later unsubscribe by following the Company´s procedures listed at the bottom of such email. 

**Business Transfers:**   
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets or businesses. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Company, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that are transferred. 

**Protection of Company and Others:**   
We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**With Your Consent:**   
Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties. 

**Is Information About Me Secure?**   
If you are a registered user, your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer. 

Only employees who need Personal Information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**   
As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Company features. 

If you add or update certain information on pages, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 

If you are a registered user of Company´s services, you may request deletion of your Company account by [contacting us](https://www.nileguide.com/contact/). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as revisions to this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Company website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if you do not enable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features. 

**Can Children Use Company´s Services?**   
Our site and the services available through the Company are not intended for children under the age of 13. Company does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents´ consent before giving out any Personal Information. We encourage you to participate in your child´s web experience. Company recommends that parents use Web filtering technology to supervise their kids´ access to the Web. 

**Conditions of Use**   
If you decide to visit Company´s site, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages and liability. 

**Third Party Sites**   
The service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Company site. In addition, Company has partnered with third party business to provide certain services to you, which may be integrated into the Company service. These other websites and third party service providers are not under Company control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Company of those other websites, the services offered through them, or their privacy practices. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Company site are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Company is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. Company recommends that you carefully review any third party terms of use and privacy policies prior to submitting your Personal Information to such third party websites. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
Company may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. You are responsible for ensuring that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

**Questions or Concerns**   
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Company site, please [contact us](https://www.nileguide.com/contact/). Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
